JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Episode 49
One More Time
I'm sorry,
Itadori-kun.
Tsk.
He's fast!
I can't figure out the
trick to his technique!
With him overwhelming
me this badly already,
he's not likely to reveal his hand, either.
I have no chance to use Convergence!
None of my external Blood
Manipulation is usable here!
You're persistent.
Seriously, what are you?
An older brother.
To nine other siblings.
Flowing Red Scale - Stack!
Flowing Red Scale - Stack
That ain't an answer.
I was asking about
your toughness and that technique...
He's starting to match me.
I see.
Flowing Red Scale, huh?
He's focusing that power
on his external eye muscles
to improve his kinetic vision.
Too bad.
I'm setting motions on the
assumption of a counter.
You're persistent, so I
went ahead and used it.
My weapon.
You've got Blood Manipulation,
so staunching blood flow
should be your forte.
Let's find out how well you fare against me
while distracted with
staunching your bleeding.
You came well prepared.
Keep it a secret.
Honestly, I think it's lame.
A sorcerer walking around with a weapon?
Feels strange if you can't win without it.
A surprising number of
people share this idea.
My own older brothers are pathetic,
carrying them around.
Yet they think they have any right
to complain about Toji-kun.
You hate them, don't you? Your brothers?
I do.
Older brothers who are less competent
than a younger brother serve no purpose.
They deserve to be hung.
You might be who you are now
thanks to those older brothers.
Huh?
Did you just say something super disgusting?
I'm grossed out.
Competent or not, older brothers
serve as an example to their younger brother.
If I go down the wrong path,
then my little brothers
can just avoid that path.
And if I go down the proper path,
then my little brothers can follow after me.
What would you do
if you were strong because your
older brothers proved weak?
You asked me why I'm so tough?
I'll tell you.
I never had an example.
I had to make many, many, many mistakes.
Yet I always had to keep
walking in front of my brothers.
That's why I'm strong!
What's he on about?
How's he still alive after bleeding so much?
The Death Paintings are
a mix of curse and human.
They possess the unique ability to
convert cursed energy into blood.
Until their cursed energy dries up,
they cannot die from blood loss.
My legs are heavy?!
Did he harden the blood that
seeped into the fabric?!
You get it, right?
It's checkmate.
I'm not sure about that.
My technique traces the motions
set ahead of time at 24 fps.
I can still move without issue
under this minor a hindrance.
Let's try it.
Why isn't he firing at me?
This was Choso's original,
developed after grappling with
his technique for 150 years.
Supernova
Sorry, but I can't understand how
you could never love your brothers.
That looks painful,
Naoya-san.
Don't look down on me!
What's this?
Poison?
Blood Manipulation shouldn't be capable of—
No! It's not a product of his technique!
He had that much blood
because he's not human!
An incarnation?!
His inhuman blood got into my
body and is being rejected!
Shall I heal you?
My reverse cursed technique
can heal people, too.
In return,
could you please report Itadori-kun's death
to the top brass, as well?
Jin!
What is it, Dad?
If you want to talk about
her, I'm going home.
Jin!
You're free to live your
life however you please.
But you have to stay away from that woman!
You'll die!
Please stop saying such mean
things in front of Yuji.
You'd be surprised at how
much a baby can remember.
I know that you've wanted a child,
and I know you were never
able to do that with Kaori.
But Kaori died—
Father, what are you talking about?
Huh? I'm...
Th-Thank goodness!
Huh?
Around September, I think?
Gojo-sensei went out of his way to see me.
He asked me to take care of you.
So I had no choice but to put on that act.
Act?
I've got a bit of a bad feeling,
so if anything happens to me,
I want you to take care of the
first- and second-years, Yuta.
Hakari? Well, he'll be fine.
If anything happens?
Troubles with women?
You've learned to joke
around, haven't you, Yuta?
No, I just can't imagine anything
happening to you, Gojo-sensei.
Take special care of Yuji Itadori.
He's been sentenced to
secret execution, like you were.
It'd be a big help if you looked out for him.
Oh, how's Miguel?
He said he didn't want to see you.
Oh.
I decided that putting on
this act was the best option
to prevent someone else from
being sent to execute you
and having information about you cut off.
Well, they're not idiots, either,
so before they would approve
me as the executioner,
HQ made me forge a pact to kill you.
So I did have to kill you for a second.
I'm real sorry about that.
Wait, then how am I alive?
The reverse cursed technique.
I used my reverse cursed technique
the moment your heart stopped
to immediately heal you.
I figured it would work,
given what I heard about you before.
There are few people who know I'm
capable of outputting positive energy.
That's right.
This is the second time
you've faked your death.
They'll probably figure it out soon,
but the situation's still chaotic.
They should consider
your death sentence carried out for a while.
Why would you go that far?
Because the people I cherish...
cherish you.
I once shouldered
a power greater than I could bear.
Though the power I thought
was forced upon me
turned out to be something
I brought upon myself.
I'm not like you.
The power you shoulder isn't your own power.
You're not to blame.
You're wrong.
It's not even a matter of blame.
I killed...
Itadori!
Fushiguro.
What are you doing?!
We're going back to Jujutsu High!
The barrier around Jujutsu
High is weakened now.
It's fine for you to return
as long as no one sees your face directly.
We'll meet up with the upperclassmen, then—
Stop it!
Don't accept what happened like it's normal.
Don't negate what happened!
I killed people.
Because of me, so many people died!
Because of us.
Of course you'd say that.
Don't go giving up by yourself.
We aren't heroes.
We're jujutsu sorcerers.
There's no one who can
judge us in a true sense.
That's all the more reason
we have to keep proving why we exist.
You're wrong, Fushiguro.
We don't have time to worry
about ourselves anymore!
If you say that, you'll...
We have to keep saving people!
...end up suffering...
I thought this was supposed to
be your driving motive, anyway!
...the whole time you remain with me!
So start by saving me,
Itadori!
Huh?
Noritoshi Kamo has set up
a death game between those
he granted cursed techniques.
The Culling Game.
Tsumiki has been drawn into this game, too.
Please, Itadori.
I need your power.
The Culling Game
1) After awakening their cursed technique,
players must go to a colony of their choice within 19 days
and pledge their participation in the culling game.
2) Players breaching the first rule shall be stripped of their technique.
3) Non-players shall become players upon entering a colony,
and their entry shall be taken as pledging to participate in the culling game.
4) Players will receive points upon ending the life of another player.
5) Points shall be designated based on the value that the game master gives their life,
and fundamentally a sorcerer will be worth 5 points
while non-sorcerers will be worth 1 point.
6) By spending 100 points,
not counting the initial point value assigned to them, players may negotiate
with the game master to add an additional rule to the culling game.
7) The game master must approve any additional rules
requested under Rule 6 above, except when the Rule
would significantly hinder the continuation of the culling game.
8) Players who do not show a change in points
within 19 days of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
The Culling Game
General Rules
Within 19 Days
Participate
Breach
Technique
Stripped
Entering a Colony
Participate
Ending
the Life
Sorcerer 5 Points
Non-Sorcerer 1 Point
The Culling Game
1) After awakening their cursed technique,
players must go to a colony of their choice within 19 days
and pledge their participation in the culling game.
2) Players breaching the first rule shall be stripped of their technique.
3) Non-players shall become players upon entering a colony,
and their entry shall be taken as pledging to participate in the culling game.
4) Players will receive points upon ending the life of another player.
5) Points shall be designated based on the value that the game master gives their life,
and fundamentally a sorcerer will be worth 5 points
while non-sorcerers will be worth 1 point.
6) By spending 100 points,
not counting the initial point value assigned to them, players may negotiate
with the game master to add an additional rule to the culling game.
7) The game master must approve any additional rules
requested under Rule 6 above, except when the Rule
would significantly hinder the continuation of the culling game.
8) Players who do not show a change in points
within 19 days of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Please, Itadori.
I need your power.
Okkotsu-senpai.
Sukuna is plotting something
that uses Fushiguro.
He was probably able to take
over my body in Shibuya
because I was force-fed ten fingers at once.
There are now 15 fingers inside me.
Even if I'm fed the remaining
five all at once,
I don't think he'll be able to take me over.
But even so,
if Sukuna does manage to take control again,
don't hesitate to kill me.
I trust you can do that, Senpai.
All right.
I'll do my best.
Fushiguro.
What do I need to do?
First, we return to Jujutsu High
and contact Tengen-sama.
How can we release the
seal of the Prison Realm?
What is Noritoshi Kamo's actual goal,
and what moves will he make?
The culling game is an unprecedented
act of jujutsu terrorism,
and we need answers to those two
questions to resolve the situation.
I think Tengen-sama's the only
one capable of answering them.
What about that woman?
Wouldn't Tsukumo-san know?
I've already spoken with Tsukumo-san.
This was her plan.
She's also hiding away at Jujutsu High.
Hiding away?
Apparently, she doesn't want
to deal with the higher-ups.
The problem is Tengen-sama's
concealment barriers.
Out of 1,000 constantly shuffling doors,
only one leads to the Tombs of the Star
where Tengen-sama resides.
So unless we can pick the right door,
we can't meet with Tengen-sama?
I'm sorry, Fushiguro.
I'm going to ask now anyway.
What happened to Kugisaki?
I see.
All right.
All right!
We might be able to do something
about the concealment barriers.
You were listening?
What do you mean, Choso?
You remember when Mahito stole
Sukuna's fingers and us
Death Paintings, right?
We'll do the same thing.
It's been... not that long, really.
Maki-senpai?!
Oh, hello.
Maki-san!
Is safe for you to be up and moving already?
Yeah, it's not an issue.
Not much I could do about the burns.
Scars remain, even with the
reverse cursed technique.
Though your Heavenly Pact of
physical prowess is impressive.
At the very end, your life was saved by
the strength of your body's endurance
rather than your resistance to curses.
It's a shame the clan head didn't make it.
It's not like it was a competition.
Megumi, how goes it with
Tengen-sama's barrier?
Well...
I'll explain.
On the way to the Tombs of the Star
is the forbidden vault holding Jujutsu High's
cursed tools and cursed objects, right?
The remains of my brothers—
Noranso, Sho-oso, Tanso,
Sanso, Kotsuso, and Shoso—
are in the forbidden vault.
Even if it's just their remains,
with all six together,
I should be able to sense their presence
using the side effect of my technique.
Good!
That's great to hear,
but who's this?
For now, you can say...
he's my older brother.
Yuji!
Let's go.
That one.
I'm certain.
My younger brothers are resting beyond here.
I'm opening it.
Yeah.
Let's head down.
There's an elevator leading to
the Tombs of the Star further in.
Choso.
I know.
I'll come back for you later.
Please wait a little longer.
Blood stains?
Did something happen?
It was twelve years ago.
Thinking back,
all of the distortions may
have started back then.
All right, everyone,
the main hall is up ahead.
There's nothing here.
This is the main hall?
No, he's rejecting us.
Tengen won't interfere with reality, but...
I thought it would be
possible to reach him now,
while the Six Eyes are sealed away,
but my prediction was naïve.
It's not all of us being
rejected... but just me?
Let's head back.
Tsumiki-san doesn't have time to spare.
You're leaving?
Nice to meet you.
Child of Zen'in, Descendant of Michizane,
Cursed Womb Death Painting,
and Vessel of Sukuna.
I must impose one condition.
We came here to learn how
to open the Prison Realm.
No greeting for me?
Then why is this Culling Game...
...to force the evolution of mankind...
...it's better for the rules if being
stripped means death, too.
If Sukuna does take control again,
don't hesitate to kill me.
Next Episode
About the Culling Game
Don't die out there.